Okay, here's his diaper bag...
기저귀 가방은 여기 있고
...and his Mr. Winky.
윙키 아저씨
그리고...
And...
... him. Hi!
벤도 가져가
-How did everything go?
-Great!
- 어땠어?
- 아주 좋았어
There was a projectile...
서로 토악질은 했지만
벤이 먼저 시작했다고
...throwing up incident,
but he started it.
We've gotta go.
- 그만 갈게
- 알았어
Oh, right.
참!
I've got some news.
It's about us.
해줄 말이 있어
우리에 관한 얘기야
You and me?
당신과 나?
아니, 나하고 수잔
No. Susan and me.
The other "us."
또 다른 우리 말야
그래
We're getting married.
우리 결혼해
As in, "I now pronounce you
wife and wife" married?
그럼 아내와 아내로서
서약하는 거야?
We'd like you to come.
We understand if you don't want to.
자기도 와 줬으면 좋겠어
싫다고 해도 이해해
Why wouldn't I want to come?
I had fun at the first wedding.
내가 왜 가기 싫겠어?
첫 결혼식도 재밌었는데
I just thought that
- 난 단지...
- 그렇지 않아
Why shouldn't I be happy for you?
What would it say about me...
내가 왜 기분 나쁘겠어?
자기가 결혼한다는데
기뻐해야지
...if I couldn't revel
in your joy?
나도 정말 기뻐!
And I'm reveling, baby!
Believe me!
Is your finger caught in that chair?
손가락 끼지 않았어?
Want us to go?
우리 갔으면 좋겠어?
The One With the Lesbian Wedding
This is cool.
You're actually on television.
대단하다 네가 정말
TV에 나오는 거야?
I know.
It really hit me last night.
그러게 말야
어젯밤엔 잠도 못 잤어
'우리의 삶'에
내가 나오게 되다니!
I'm on Days of our Lives.
그리곤 우리 생각을 했지
Then I started thinking about us,
and how these are the days of our lives.
우리들 삶은 어떤가 하고
Yes!
- 좋았어!
- 뭐야?
What?
캐롤의 결혼식 요리사가
자전거 사고로 깁스했대
Carol and Susan's caterer
had a bike accident...
...and she's in a
full-body cast.
좋았어!
They asked me, which is cool
since I've never catered...
내게 요리를 부탁했다고
결혼식 요리는 처음이야
...and I need the money.
Is this a problem?
요새 돈도 궁했거든
오빠 괜찮겠지?
-Would it matter?
-You're so great!
- 상관없어
- 이해할 줄 알았어!
Thank you!
고마워!
-You're really not going?
-I'm really not.
- 정말 안 갈 거야?
- 정말 안 간다니까
They already live together.
Why do they need to get married?
지금도 같이 살면서
결혼식은 뭐 하러 해?
They love each other.
서로 사랑하니까
주위 사람들 앞에서
사랑을 확인하는 거라고
They wanna celebrate that love
with the people close to them.
If you wanna call
that a reason.
그게 이유가 될까?
Who's the bitterest
man in the living room?
누구는 배 아프겠다
정말 배 아프겠어
The bitterest man
in the living room?
누구는 배 아프대요!
Hi, neighbor.
안녕, 사촌
-I thought you were over this.
-That has nothing to do with it.
이미 잊은 줄 알았는데
그거하곤 상관없어
내 전처란 말야
If she were marrying a guy,
you wouldn't expect me to go.
남자와 결혼했다면
나보고 가라고 했겠어?
남자랑 결혼한다면
레즈비언도 아니겠지
If she were marrying a guy,
she'd be the worst lesbian ever.
Did I miss it?
끝났어?
No, I'm on right after this guy
shoots himself.
아냐, 이 남자가 자살하면
내가 나올 거야
야, 쌈박한데
She's pretty.
인간성도 좋아
카메라 앞에 서는 법과
And she's really nice.
She taught me about
how to work with the cameras...
방귀 냄새 맡는
표정연기도 가르쳐 줬어
...and smell-the-fart acting.
- 뭘 가르쳐 줬다고?
- 뭐라고?
-I'm sorry, what?
-Excuse me?
You got so many lines
to learn so fast that sometimes...
대사가 너무 많아서
외우기가 힘드니까
...you need a minute
to remember your next one.
다음 대사를 기억해 낼
시간이 필요하다고
So while you're thinking...
대사를 기억하면서
심각한 표정을 짓거든
...you take this big pause
where you look all intense.
이렇게 말야
Like this....
그렇구나
내가 나오는 장면이다!
Here's my scene!
Mrs. Wallace?
- 월레스 부인?
- 네
Dr. Drake Ramoray,
your sister's neurosurgeon.
라모레이 박사입니다
동생의 담당의죠
Is she going to be all right?
동생은 괜찮을까요?
I'm afraid the situation
is much more dire than we'd expected.
상태가 저희 생각보다
훨씬 더 심각합니다
Your sister's suffering from a...
동생 분이 앓는 병은...
두개골 혈종입니다
...subcranial hematoma.
Perhaps we can
discuss this further over coffee.
커피라도 들면서
계속 얘기를 나눌까요?
멋졌어!
Nice!
For a minute, I thought you were
actually smelling something.
정말 방귀 냄새를
맡는 줄 알았다니까
-Do it again!
-All right!
다시 해봐!
- 멋졌어!
- 다시 해봐!
-That was so good!
-Do it again.
알았어
"Damn it, Braverman!
It's right there on the chart!"
'젠장, 차트에 적혔잖아! '
I gotta get to work.
I got a big dinosaur bone to inspect.
난 출근해서 공룡 뼈나
검사해야겠어
No, that's me.
- 아냐, 그건 나잖아
- 참, 그렇지
Oh, right.
Oh, thanks. Couldn't....
고마워, 차마...
Is everything okay?
무슨 일 있었어?
No.
응, 아니...
One of my clients died
on the massage table today.
손님 한 분이 마사지를
받다가 돌아가셨어
Oh, my God!
맙소사!
마사지 받는 것보다
그게 더 편했나 보다
That's a little more relaxed
than you want them to get.
82살이셨는데
She was, you know,
82 years old...
로즈 에이들맨 부인이야
...and her name was
Mrs. Adelman.
Oh, honey.
It's just so strange. You know...
너무 이상해
이렇게 생각하셨을 거야
...she probably woke up
this morning and thought...
'아침 먹고 산책 한 후에
마사지를 받아야지'
... I'll have some breakfast,
take a walk, then have my massage.
Little did she know God thought,
"Okay, but that's it."
그런데 하나님 대답은
'그걸로 땡이야! '였다고
정말 이상한 것은
Oh, but the weirdest things was...
내가 향기 목욕을
시켜드릴 때 돌아가셨는데
... I was cleansing her aura
when it happened.
영혼이 육체를 떠나면서
멀리 못 간 것 같아
And when her spirit
left her body...
... I don't think it went very far.
What do you mean?
무슨 소리야?
I think it went into me.
내 몸에 들어온 것 같아
This is so hard.
양고기와 오리고기 중에
뭘로 해야 할지 모르겠어
I can't decide
between lamb or duck.
Well, lambs are scarier.
양은 무서워
Or the movie would've been called
Silence of the Ducks.
'양들의 침묵'이란 영화가
괜히 나왔겠어?
Okay, who ordered what?
누가 뭐 시켰어?
I had the half-drunk cappuccino
with the lipstick on the rim.
난 컵에 립스틱 묻은
반쯤 마신 카푸치노
And this with the cigarette
butt in it, is that decaf?
담배꽁초가 들은 것이
디카페야?
맙소사!
Oh, God.
You're so uptight
about your mom coming.
엄마가 오신다고
너무 긴장한 거 아냐?
I know. I just don't want
her to think that because...
처음 오시는 거라 그래
배리와 결혼 안 해서
내 인생 망쳤다고 하실까 봐
... I didn't marry Barry
my life is crap.
Talk about crap, just
listen to Stella Neidman...
인생 망쳤대서 말인데
스텔라에게 로드의 얘길
한 백 번 해줘 봐
...tell her story about Rod Steiger
for the hundredth time.
피비, 그 할머니
언제까지 계신대?
Pheebs? How long do you think
this lady will be with us?
I don't know. She obviously
has some unfinished business.
몰라, 이승에서 못 다한
일이 많으셨나 봐
Sit up!
똑바로 앉아!
There she is!
안녕?
-Mom!
-Hey, sweetie!
- 엄마!
- 내 귀여운 딸!
여기가 네 직장이구나
잘 꾸며놨네
So this is where you work!
Oh, it's wonderful!
Is it a living room?
Is it a restaurant? Who can tell?
거실인지 카페인지
분간이 안 되잖니
그게 매력이겠지만
I guess that's the fun.
Pretty much.
Here, meet my friends.
맞아요
여긴 내 친구들이에요
Monica! You look gorgeous!
모니카!
너 정말 예뻐졌구나!
마지막으로 봤을 때는
살덩어리였는데
Oh, my! The last time I saw you,
it was eat or be eaten.
This is Joey.
얘는 조이고
This is Phoebe.
얘는 피비, 얘는 챈들러
로스는 아시죠?
This is Chandler.
You remember Ross?
- 안녕, 로스
- 안녕하세요, 아줌마
Oh, hello, Ross.
Mrs. Greene.
그런데...
What do you think of my
daughter, in the apron...
앞치마를 두르고 일하는
내 딸의 모습 좀 보렴!
...with the big job!
- 그만 해, 엄마!
- 알았어
Oh, Mom!
If you didn't pour the coffee,
no one would have anything to drink.
너 아니면 아무도 커피 한잔
마시지 못했을 거야
Believe me, sometimes that happens.
가끔 있어도 못 마실 때가 있죠
This is just so exciting!
You know, I never worked.
난 이런 일을 해본 적이
없어서 참 신기해!
I went from my father's house
to the sorority house...
집에만 있다가
시집을 갔거든
...to my husband's house.
I am just so proud of you!
너무 대견스럽구나
- 정말로요?
- 그럼
Really?
I know who you remind me of.
당신하고 닮은 사람이 있수
Evelyn Durmer.
에벌린 더머!
That's before the lousy face-lift.
Now she looks like Soupy Sales.
안면성형수술을 받아서
지금은 수피 세일 같지만
에벌린 더머가 누구야?
Pheebs? Who's Evelyn Durmer?
I don't know.
Who's Soupy Sales?
나도 몰라
수피 세일은 누구지?
Oh, my God!
맙소사!
There's an unattractive
nude man playing the cello.
창 밖의 남자가
나체로 첼로를 켜고 있어
Just be glad he's not playing
a smaller instrument.
조그만 자기 물건으로
안 하는 게 다행이네
You have some life here, sweetie!
너 정말 잘 살고 있구나!
Mom, I realize you were upset
when I didn't marry Barry...
내가 배리랑 결혼해서
안정적으로 살지 않아서
...and get the house in the suburbs
with all the security.
엄마가 화났던 것은
이해하지만
난 이 생활이 더 좋아요
This is just
so much better for me.
엄마도 안다
배리를 사랑하지 않았지
I know.
You didn't love Barry, honey.
And I've never seen you this happy.
네가 이렇게 행복한 건
처음 보는구나
나도 이렇게 사는 것이
너무나 좋을 것 같아
I look at you and I think,
"This is what I want."
For me.
저요?
꼭 네 얘기는 아냐
Well, not just for you.
What do you mean?
무슨 뜻이죠?
I'm considering
leaving your father.
아빠랑 헤어질 생각이란다
All right, tell me
if this is too cute.
네 생각은 어때?
Lesbian wedding...
chicken breasts.
레즈비언 결혼식을 위한
새가슴 요리!
Oh, God.
I think I'm gonna be sick.
맙소사...
토할 것 같아
왜? 젖꼭지는 제거하고
요리할 건데
What? It's not like I'm putting
little nipples on them.
-You had no idea?
-None.
- 넌 전혀 눈치 못 챘어?
- 응
They didn't fight?
- 자주 다투셨어?
- 아니, 서로 말도 안 하셔
No, they didn't even
talk to each other.
How was I suppose to know
they were having problems?
두 분에게 문제 있는 걸
내가 어떻게 알았겠어?
내가 젊었을 땐
이혼은 상상도 못했어
You know, in my day,
divorce was not an option.
또 나타나셨네
Hey, look who's up!
I just can't believe
this is happening!
이해할 수가 없어
어렸을 때 친구들 부모님이
다 이혼했어도
When I was little,
all parents got divorced.
우리 집엔 그런 문제가
없을 줄 알았거든
I figured as an adult,
I wouldn't have to worry about it.
Can't you look at this
as flattering?
좋게 생각할 수도 있잖아
어머니가 너처럼
되고 싶어하신다고
She just wants to be like you.
그럼 내 머리스타일만
따라하면 되잖아
Well, couldn't she have just
copied my haircut?
When my parents divorced,
they sent me to a shrink...
난 부모님이 이혼하고
정신과 치료를 받았는데
아이들은 자신들 탓으로
돌리는 경향이 있대
...and she told me
that kids blame themselves.
But in your case,
it's actually kind of true.
네 경우에는
그 말이 맞는 것 같아
Oh, that's him.
오셨어!
Damn! My mail-order
grandfather hasn't come yet.
이런, 내가 통신 주문한
할아버진 아직 안 왔는데
-Phoebe?
-Hi, Mr. Adelman.
- 피비?
- 네, 에이들맨 씨
-Nice to see you.
-Thanks for coming.
- 만나서 반갑수
- 와 주셔서 감사해요
괜찮아, 빈둥거릴 시간이
줄어들기는 했지만
That's okay. Although you did
cut into my busy day of sitting.
앉으시겠어요?
Do you wanna sit?
아니, 난 오전 시간을
서서 보내거든
No, I spent most of my morning
trying to stand up.
무슨 일이지?
What can I do
for you, my dear?
어떻게 말해야 될지
모르겠네요
Okay, I don't know how
to say this, but....
할머니의 영혼이
제 몸으로 들어오셨어요
I think when your wife's spirit
left her body...
...it kind of stuck around...
...in me.
자네 몸 속에
할망구가 들었다고?
You're saying
my wife is in you?
Yeah. You don't have to
believe me, but...
네, 안 믿으셔도 좋아요
할머니에게 할 일이
남아 있으셨나요?
...can you think of
any unfinished business she had?
영혼이 떠나지 못하는
이유라도 있나요?
Any reason to hang around?
I don't know what to say.
나도 잘은 모르겠지만
All I can think of is that...
죽기 전에 그랬지
...she used to say that before she died,
she wanted to see everything.
모든 것을 보고 싶다고
-Everything?
-Everything.
- 모든 것을요?
- 전부 다
그럼 너무 많은데
That's a lot of stuff.
Oh, wait, l....
참, 나랑 마지막으로
관계를 갖고 싶다고 했어
I remember she also said she wanted
to sleep with me one last time.
I'm sorry.
There's laughing in my head.
죄송하지만
머리에서 웃으래요
시도는 괜찮았지?
Worth a shot, huh?
Look at this!
이걸 보렴!
These are all Halloween,
three years ago.
3년 전 할로윈 때 찍은
사진이에요
배리 사진도 있는데
병원에서 곧장 왔니?
Oh, and look, here's Barry.
He came straight
from the office?
아니, 할로윈 복장이야
Oh, no.
That was his costume.
실제로 치과 의사인데
치과 의사 복장을 했었지
See, he's actually an orthodontist,
but he came as a regular dentist.
내가 도움은 필요 없다고
말한 적 있지?
You guys?
Remember when I said
that I don't need your help?
아니, 이렇게 말했잖아
'부엌에 얼씬거리지 마! '
Actually, I think you said...
... "Don't touch that
and get out of my kitchen."
Really? Weird.
Anyway....
내가?
거 이상하네
I planned really well.
I planned and planned.
만반의 계획을 세웠는데
I just didn't plan
enough time to do it.
그 계획을 실행하는 데
시간이 너무 부족해
- 도와 줘?
- 네가 그러고 싶으면
-You want some help?
-lf you want.
정말 힘든 하루였어
구경 안 한 데가 없다니까
What a day!
I took her everywhere.
박물관, 록펠러 센터
자유의 여신상...
The Museum of Modern Art,
Rockefeller Center...
...the Statue of Liberty.
She's still with you?
아직도 몸 안에 계셔?
응, 아직도 볼 것이
남으셨나 봐
Yes. I guess she hasn't
seen everything yet.
잠깐만, 할머니가 또
화장실에 가고 싶대
Be right back. She has to go
to the bathroom again.
참하게도 생겼네!
Such a pretty face!
Oh, this is so much fun!
Just the girls!
너무나 재미있구나
여자끼리 사니까
Do you know what we should do?
Does anybody have any marijuana?
더 재밌게 지내자고
혹시 대마초 있니?
God!
어머!
Look, no one's smoking pot
around all this food.
음식 옆에서 피우시면 안 돼요
Well, that's fine.
알았다
한 번도 피워 보지 않아서
해보려고
I never did it.
I just thought I might.
요즘 섹스는 어떻게 하지?
What's new in sex?
섹스를 어떻게 하냐고요?
엄마에게는 네 아빠가
유일한 남자였거든
The only man I've been with
is your father.
I'm dicing. I'm dicing.
I don't hear anything.
전 칼질하느라 바빠서
아무것도 못 들어요
네 아빠 탓하는 게 아니라
This is no offense to your dad,
but I was thinking...
새로운 것이 있을까
궁금해서 말야
...there might be more.
You know what? I cannot
have this conversation with you.
엄마랑 이런 대화는
정말 하기 싫어!
알았어, 알았다고
All right.
아빠와 이혼한다고
폭탄선언을 하고
You come here and drop this bomb on me
before you even tell Daddy.
- 축하해 드리길 바랬어요?
- 아냐!
Do you want my blessing?
Want me to talk you out of it?
그럼 말려 주길 바래요?
- 아냐!
- 그럼 대체 뭐죠?
Then what do you want?
난 네가 이해할 거라
생각했었다
I guess I figured
you would understand.
Why on earth
would I understand this?
내가 어떻게 그걸
이해할 수 있겠어요?
You didn't marry your Barry, honey.
넌 배리가 싫다고
결혼하지 않았지만
난 네 아빠와 결혼했어
But I married mine.
비상사태야!
We're in trouble. We've only got
12 hours and 36 minutes left.
12시간 36분 남았어
동작 봐라!
Move, move, move!
모니카, 독일 병정이
소원이었어?
I feel like you should
have German subtitles.
조이, 서둘러!
Joey, speed it up!
I'm sorry! It's the pigs!
They're reluctant to get in the blanket!
돼지들이 이불 속으로
들어가기 싫다잖아!
How did this happen?
I thought you had this planned out.
다 계획했다고 하더니
어쩌다 이렇게 됐어?
Do you want me to cry?
내가 울기를 바래?
Is that what you want?
그걸 원해?
내가 우는 모습을
보고 싶어?
Do you wanna see me cry?
아닙니다, 장군님!
Sir, no, sir!
All right, you!
오빠!
No. Look, I told you,
I am not a part of this thing.
난 빠진다고 분명히
말했을 텐데
Look, Ross. I know you have issues with
Carol and Susan, and I feel for you.
캐롤과 수잔의 일로
상처받은 건 알겠지만
But if you don't help,
I'm gonna take those hot dogs...
날 도와 주지 않으면
저 핫도그로
'로스와 돼지 말이'란
음식을 만들 거야!
...and create an appetizer
called "Pigs In Ross."
All right, ball a melon!
수박 속을 파
How come I'm stuck dicing
when he gets to ball a melon?
난 종일 썰어대는데
로스는 수박 속을 파?
- 어떻게 돼가요?
- 계획대로 잘되고 있어요
-How's it going?
-Great! Right on schedule.
Got my little happy helpers.
친구들이 자청해서
돕고 있거든요
That's fine. Whatever.
그렇군요
왜 그래?
What's wrong?
Nothing.
아무것도 아냐
모든 게 엉망이야
결혼식을 취소할까 봐
Okay, everything.
I think we're calling off the wedding.
뭐?
You're still gonna pay me, right?
그래도 수고비는 주겠죠?
Or something a little less selfish.
성의의 표시라도
What's the matter?
What happened?
대체 무슨 일이야?
My parents called to say
they weren't coming.
- 부모님이 안 오시겠대
- 저런!
내가 레즈비언인 걸
싫어하시는 건 알지만
I knew they were
having trouble with this, but...
...they're my parents.
They're supposed to give me away.
부모님이 참석 안 하시면
무슨 의미가 있겠어
진정해
Susan and I fought because
I said maybe we should call it off.
결혼식을 취소하자고 했다고
캐롤과 대판 싸웠어
She said, "This isn't for them.
It's for us."
우리를 위한 결혼식인데
부모님이 맘에 걸리면
And if I couldn't see that,
we should cancel the wedding.
취소하는 게 좋을 것 같아
I don't know what to do.
어떻게 할지 모르겠어
I can't believe I'm gonna say this,
but I think Susan's right.
이런 말해서 미안하지만
수잔이 옳은 것 같아
You do?
그럴까?
수잔을 사랑하지?
너무 강조할 필요는 없고
Do you love her? And don't be
too emphatic about this.
- 사랑하고말고
- 그럼 됐잖아
Of course I do.
Well then, that's it.
If George and Adelaide can't
accept that, then the hell with them.
부모님이 반대하셔도
그건 부모님 문제야
만약 우리 부모님이
너와의 결혼을 반대했어도
If my parents didn't want me
to marry you...
... no way that would've
stopped me.
난 그냥 했을 거야
네 결혼이야
생각대로 밀고 나가
Look, this is your wedding.
Do it.
맞아, 당신 말이 백 번 옳아
You're right.
Of course you're right.
So we're back on?
- 그럼 하는 거예요?
- 그래요
We're back on.
다들 들었지?
잽싸게 지지고 볶아!
You heard the woman!
Peel! Chop! Devil!
2분이나 손해봤잖아
Can't believe
I lost two minutes!
속 빈 강정이야
It just seems so futile.
여자들이 이리 많아도
그림의 떡이잖아
You know?
All these women, and nothing!
I feel like Superman
without my powers, you know?
초능력을 잃어버린
슈퍼맨이 된 기분이야
I have the cape,
and yet I cannot fly.
망토는 걸쳤지만
하늘을 날 수가 없다고
Well, now you understand
how I feel every single day.
이제 매일 밤 내 기분을
이해할 수 있겠지?
난 매일 밤이
레즈비언의 결혼식이라고
The world is my lesbian wedding.
버터스카치 들라우?
Butterscotch?
No one?
없어요?
나중에 후회할 거면서
All right,
you'll be sorry later.
- 고마워
- 아냐
-Thank you.
-Anytime.
Ross.
로스?
Nothing makes God happier...
하나님께서 두 사람의
결혼을 축복하십니다
...than when two people, any two people,
come together in love.
가족, 친지 여러분
Friends, family,
we're gathered here today...
오늘 캐롤과 수잔이
성스러운 결혼을 합니다
...to join Carol and Susan
in holy matrimony.
Oh, my God!
맙소사!
Now I've seen everything!
이제야 모든 걸 봤네 그랴!
떠나셨어
할머니가 떠났어!
She's gone!
She's gone.
신경 쓰지 말고 결혼해요
얼른요
Go ahead, get married.
Go, go!
Strangers in the night
Exchanging glances
Wondering in the night
Would you look at them?
- 두 사람을 봐
- 그래, 행복해 보여
Yeah. Can't help but.
'돼지고기 쌈' 맛있어요?
How's that pig-in-the-blanket
working out for you?
내가 직접 싼 놈들이죠
I wrapped those bad boys.
I miss Rose.
- 로즈 할머니가 그리워
- 그래?
Oh, yeah?
I know it's kind of weird, but
she was a big part of my life....
이상하긴 했지만
내 몸의 일부였잖아
너무나 외로워
I don't know, I feel alone.
방금 두 분의 대화를
들었는데
You know, I couldn't help
overhearing what you just said.
로즈는 그만 잊어버리고
삶을 되찾아요
I think it's time you forget about Rose,
move on with your life.
How about we get you a drink?
나와 한잔하겠어요?
Okay. So nice!
좋아요
꼬시려고 해봐야
헛수고겠죠?
I shouldn't even bother
coming up with a line, right?
엄마, 재미있어요?
Hey, Mom, having fun?
재밌다 뿐이니!
Am l! I just danced
with a wonderfully large woman.
방금 덩치 큰 여자와
춤을 췄거든
여자 세 명이 식사 중에
내게 눈길을 주더라
And three other girls
made eyes at me over at the buffet.
내가 그런 성적기호를
가지진 않았지만
I'm not saying
it's something I wanna pursue...
선택의 여지가 있다니
기분이 좋아지더라고
... but it's nice to know
I have options.
There's more alcohol, right?
술 남았지?
- 어때?
- 좋아
How you doing?
오늘 고마웠어
You did a good thing today.
You wanna dance?
나랑 출래?
아냐, 난 됐어
No, that's fine.
그러지 말고
Come on.
네가 리드하게 해줄게
I'll let you lead.
알았어
Look, penis, schmenis!
남자든 여자든
다 똑같은 사람이잖아요
Okay? We're all people.
Which one of us is gonna be
the first one to get married?
우리 중에서 누가 먼저
결혼할까?
난 벌써 결혼했었어
Mon, I was married.
-Yeah, me too, technically.
-I had a wedding.
서류상으론 나도야
난 결혼식만 했어
Just trying to
start a discussion.
그냥 할 얘기 없어서 해봤어
Which one do you think
will be the last to get married?
이건 어때?
우리 중에 누가 가장
늦게 결혼할까?
벤도 포함하는 거지?
Isn't Ben in this?
Of course!
- 그럼
- 당연하지!
Absolutely.